Classes Collection UA039
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Classes, 1816 -- 2022; 1857 -- 2000; UA039.001; 32.45 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 10 Digital Object(s) Of the 10 digital objects in this series, 2 have extent information comprising 18 files.; 56.0 Megabytes Of the 10 digital objects in this series, 2 have extent information comprising 67.7 MB.
  - Classes of 1910-1919, 1908 -- 1972; UA039.001.007
    - Classes (3), 1912; UA039.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
      Programs, Class Day; calendar.
    - Classes, 1912; UA039.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
      Hand-made scrap-book, 1912.
    - Classes, 1913; UA039.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
      Program, Junior Day; class song; Junior Book; program, invitation, music, Class Day; calandar; 50th reunion. booklet; commencement booklet.
    - Classes (1 of 2), 1914; UA039.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
      Program, invitation, history, Class Day; program, First Annual Banquet of the Class of 1914; program, commencement; Program, Class Day (Medical School); "Junior Street Fair"; 50th Anniversary; Alumni Weekend
    - Classes (2 of 2), 1914; UA039.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
      Newspaper clippings; calendar; 25th reunion; 50th reunion, program, Class Day.
    - Classes (1 of 2), 1915; UA039.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
      Ivy Society booklet; program, music, Class day; Junior book; newspaper clippings; program, Junior Day; Junior Book; class song; correspondence; class calandar.
    - Classes (2 of 2), 1915; UA039.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
      50th reunion booklet; calendar; Junior Prom Committee planning sheet; Tufts songs; 1915 Class Day Program of the Medical and Dental Schools.
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      1915 Class Day Program of the Medical and Dental Schools gift of Francis Connor, 2018, accession UA-2019-018.
    - Classes (1 of 2), 1916; UA039.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
      Newspaper clippings; "Pygmalion and Galatea"; program, Junior Day; 40th reunion; invitation, commencement; Program, music, Calss Day; class song; Alma Mater's Song; 50th reunion.
    - Classes (2 of 2), 1916; UA039.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
      Program, Class Day; class book; calendar.
    - Classes (3), 1916; UA039.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
      Book of poetry; "Songs of 1916 30th Reunion"; 50th reunion.
    - Classes, 1917; UA039.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
      Program, Junior Day; program, "Meisterschaft"; Freshman Theatricals; calendar; 50th reunion; calandar; correspondence. Added accession 2009.002 on 2008-07-09, 4 slides from 40th reunion donated by Gina Stanton, granddaughter of alum Charles I. Stanton Sr.
    - Classes, 1918; UA039.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
      Play, "Much Ado About Nothing"; Freshman Theatricles; cheers, music-Class Day; biographical sketches:members of Tufts College class 1918; 30th reunion; 50th reunion; class calendar.
    - Classes, 1919; UA039.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
      Invitation, commencement; program, music, exersises-Class day; 50th reuinion; correspondence.
    - Class of 1910 photographs, 1908 -- 1910; UA039.001.053.00004 (Box 53)
    - Class of 1910 photographs, 1935 -- 1965; UA039.001.053.00005 (Box 53)
    - Class of 1911 photographs, 1910 -- 1961; UA039.001.053.00006 (Box 53)
      See also: Box 65 Item 2 (oversized Class of 1911 photograph).
    - Class of 1912 photographs, 1962 -- 1967; UA039.001.053.00007 (Box 53)
    - Class of 1913 photographs, 1963 -- 1968; UA039.001.054.00001 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1914 photographs, 1914 -- 1964; UA039.001.054.00002 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1915 photographs, 1955 -- 1965; UA039.001.054.00003 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1915 photographs, 1940 -- 1965; UA039.001.054.00004 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1915 photographs, 1912; UA039.001.054.00005 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1916 photographs, 1916 -- 1961; UA039.001.054.00006 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1916 photographs, UA039.001.054.00007 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1917 photographs, 1962 -- 1967; UA039.001.054.00008 (Box 54)
    - Class of 1916 reunion photograph, UA039.001.054.00012 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
    - Class of 1913, UA039.001.054.00013 (Box Shared 4)
    - Class of 1918 photographs, 1915 -- 1968; UA039.001.055.00001 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1918 photographs, 1928; UA039.001.055.00002 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1919 photographs, 1959 -- 1969; UA039.001.055.00003 (Box 55)
    - Photograph, Class of 1911, UA039.001.065.00002 (Box Shared 66)
      Located in UIP Box 80 oversized photos
    - Embroidered Tufts Medical Seal, 1919; UA039.001.065.00003 (Box Shared 66)
      The embroidered medical seal was given to Dr. Naaman Steinberg upon his graduation from Tufts Medical School in 1919. Seal was sewed by a family member. Embroidery folded up amidst tissue paper (no folder). Seal was donated by Dr. Naaman Steinberg's, M 1919, daughter, Elizabeth Schwartzman in 2007; seal arrived at DCA via Cora C. Ho, MLS Deputy Director, HHSL (accession number 2007.022). Because the embroidery was smelling of mold when it arrived at DCA, it was removed from its frame, dried, and then stored in the box. The embroidery is stored in UIP/box 088.
    - Tufts College Military Units, Photographs, 1918; UA039.001.077.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
      These items were found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Company A, S.A.T.C., U.S.A., Tufts College, 1918; U.S. Naval Unit, S.A.T.C., Tufts College, 1918; Tufts College Training Detachment, New Hampshire Contingent, n.d.; Company C, S.A.T.C., U.S.A., Tufts College, 1918; Tufts College Training Detachment, September, 1918; Company B, S.A.T.C., U.S.A., Tufts College, 1918; Unidentified Military Unit, 1918. Old orange barcode number 39090014015206o.
    - Tufts College Alumni, Hotel Astor, 1910, UA039.001.077.00003 (Box Shared 35)
      - Tufts College alumni at the Hotel Astor, 1910; UA039.001.077.00003.00001; Drucker & Co. (Box Shared 35)
        People; Alumni and alumnae; Tufts College
    - Studio portrait, men in suits and ties, 1910 -- 1911; UA039.001.080.00004 (Box Shared 38)
      It is unclear if this is the class of 1910-1911.
    - Tufts College and Jackson College, class of 1911, UA039.001.080.00005 (Box Shared 38)
    - Tufts College, class of 1914, UA039.001.080.00007 (Box Shared 38)
      This photograph is attached to the back of an old scrapbook.
    - Dean men at Tufts, 1904 -- 1914; UA039.001.080.00009 (Box Shared 38)
      Inscription on photo: "Dean men at Tufts, banquet given by Mr. Peirce, April 4, 1914, (Young's Hotel, Boston)."
    - Studio portrait, men in graduation gowns, 1910 -- 1920; UA039.001.080.00010 (Box Shared 38)
      It is unclear if this is a class photograph. The dates are approximate.
    - Studio portrait, men in suits and ties, 1913 -- 1914; UA039.001.080.00011 (Box Shared 38)
      It is unclear if this is a class photograph. In fragile condition, evidence of mildew although not active. May need preservation work at some point.
    - William J. Bennett, class of 1914, portraitin United States military uniform, 1917 -- 1918; UA039.001.080.00020 (Box Shared 38)
      The dates are approximate.
    - 25th reunion, class of 1910, 1935; UA039.001.080.00022 (Box Shared 36)
      This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - Reunion parade, men in clown makeup, 1935; UA039.001.080.00023 (Box Shared 36)
      This date is approximate. Appears to be the same event as item 22. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - Reunion parade, shot of street, 1935; UA039.001.080.00024 (Box Shared 36)
      The date is approximate. Appears to be same event as items 22 and 23. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - 25th reunion, class of 1910, close-up, 1935; UA039.001.080.00025 (Box Shared 36)
    - Herbert Armstrong, Class of 1916, photographs and award, 1913 -- 1916, 1972; UA039.000504 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
      Gift of Andrew C. Armstrong, 2019, accession UA-2019-058.
      This file includes photographs of the Tufts baseball team and Delta Tau Delta fraternity and the Tufts Jumbo Club Award.
  - Classes of 1920-1929, 1919 -- 1979; UA039.001.008
    - Classes (1), 1920; UA039.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
      Program, music-Class day; 15th anniversary; calandar.
    - Classes (2), 1920; UA039.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
      35th reunion; 40th reunion.
    - Classes (1), 1921; UA039.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
      Program, Class Day; play, "A Comedy of Errors"; program, Junior Day; advertisement, Alumni Field Day; 20th reunion; 45th reunion; 50th reunion.
    - Classes (2), 1921; UA039.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
      13th anniversary report.
    - Classes (1), 1922; UA039.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
      Class Calandar; Freshman Class play program, " The Importance of Being Earnest"; program, Class day; ticket application, Alumni Field Day; advert, Alumni Field Day; 45th reunion booklet, Jackson College; correspondence.
    - Classes (2), 1922; UA039.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
      50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1923; UA039.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
      Class calandar; program, Class Day; invitation, Commencement; program, Junior Day; invitation, Class Day; Class Song of 1923, "The Pledge of Loyalty"; report, 45th reunion Jackson College; report, 50th reuinion Jackson College; notice, concerning class day tickets; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1924; UA039.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
      Leather-bound booklet, Class Day; Napkins from fortieth and forty-fifth reunions; Class calandra; invitation, Senior Promenade; invitation, Class Day; program, Commencement Season; program, Class of 1924 play "Joint Owners in Spain"; program, Class Day; correspondence; (In MS041/001-001#00009 There are three 50th reunion name tags/buttons.)
    - Classes, 1925; UA039.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
      Senior Class "Who's Who" list; announcement, Commencement Season; 50th anniversary program; class notes; program, Class Day.
    - Classes, 1926; UA039.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
      Program, Class day; music, Class Day; 10th reunion booklet; 15th reunion booklet; 25 reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1927; UA039.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
      Program, Class day; 25th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1927; UA039.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
      35th reunion booklet; 45th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1928; UA039.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
      Dance card, Senior Promenade; program, Class day; "Memories, Class Song of 1928; report of Senior Prom and Class day committee; 25 reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet; class day book; photo of Leo Green.
    - Classes, 1929; UA039.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
      Program, ticket, and Chapel Exercises, Class day; report, Class Day and Promenade committee; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1929; UA039.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
      40th reunion information.
    - Class of 1920 photographs, 1919 -- 1970; UA039.001.055.00004 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1921 photographs, 1921 -- 1971; UA039.001.055.00005 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1922 photographs, 1921 -- 1967; UA039.001.055.00006 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1923 photographs, 1922 -- 1968; UA039.001.055.00007 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1924 photographs, 1921 -- 1969; UA039.001.055.00008 (Box 55)
    - Class of 1924 photographs, 1921 -- 1974; UA039.001.055.00009 (Box 55)
    - Photo Album by Esther Dorothy Fowler, J 1923, 1919 -- 1924; UA039.001.055.00010 (Box 55)
      The photo album was found by Hannah Myers in a dumpster in Amherst, Mass., and sent to Tufts DCA in April 2007. Date is approximate
    - Class of 1925 photographs, 1921 -- 1923; UA039.001.056.00001 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1925 photographs, UA039.001.056.00002 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1925 photographs, 1925 -- 1970; UA039.001.056.00003 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1925 photographs, 1960 -- 1975; UA039.001.056.00004 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1925 photographs, 1921 -- 1925; UA039.001.056.00005 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1925 photographs, 1921 -- 1924; UA039.001.056.00006 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1926 photographs, 1976; UA039.001.056.00007 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1926 photographs, 1936 -- 1976; UA039.001.056.00008 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1926 photographs, 1926 -- 1961; UA039.001.056.00009 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1927 photographs, 1967 -- 1977; UA039.001.056.00010 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1927 photographs, 1927 -- 1967; UA039.001.056.00011 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1928 photographs, 1968 -- 1978; UA039.001.056.00012 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1929 photographs, 1928 -- 1979; UA039.001.056.00013 (Box 56)
    - Jackson College Pan-Hellenic Council, 1928, UA039.001.056.00016 (Box 56)
      Photograph found in 1928 Jumbo yearbook owned by Virginia Call, J '28. Call was on the Jackson Pan-Hellenic Council.
      photographic print
    - Jackson College Athletic Association, 1928, UA039.001.056.00017 (Box 56)
      Photograph found in 1928 Jumbo yearbook owned by Virginia Call, J '28. Call was a member of the Jackson College Athletic Association.
    - Jackson College Student Government, 1928, UA039.001.056.00018 (Box 56)
      Photograph found in 1928 Jumbo yearbook owned by Virginia Call, J '28. Call was on the Jackson College student government.
    - Jackson College Senior Class, 1928, UA039.001.056.00019 (Box 56)
      Photograph found in 1928 Jumbo yearbook owned by Virginia Call, J '28. Call graduated in this year and is in the photograph.
    - Jackson athletics sweater, awarded to Persis Judd., 1927; UA039.001.070 (Box 70)
    - Alumni Frolic, outside Bowen Porch, 1920; UA039.001.077.00004 (Box Shared 4)
    - First informal sing on the reservoir terrace, 1920-06; UA039.001.080.00013 (Box Shared 38)
      Inscription on photo: "First informal sing on the reservoir terrace. Thursday, June 8, 1920, 7-8 pm. Showing about one-third of the students who were there."
    - Poster with photographs of Dr. John T. Blake, UA039.001.080.00019 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
      John T. Blake is a 1921 Tufts alumni from the Engineering School. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. Note the different location of this item; it is located in an oversize folder in the map case. No Date Available
    - Bright Lights Society, Robinson Hall, engineering school, 1920 -- 1930; UA039.001.080.00021 (Box Shared 36)
      These dates are approximate. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - Reunion, class of 1920, women, 1935; UA039.001.080.00026 (Box Shared 36)
      This date is approximate. Appears to be the same event as items 22-25. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - 1929 Class Day Book, UA039.001.086.00006 (Box 86)
      Belonged to Lydia Risi. Donated by niece Roberta Walters.
    - William Gambino E'26 photographs, student records, and diploma, circa 1920 -- 1942; UA039.001.007.00009; .3 Linear Feet 1 folder, 1 oversize folder (Box 7, Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 10)
      Donated by the Gurrisi family, 2016, accession UA-2017-020.
      This file includes William Gambino's (BS, Electrical Engineering, 1926) graduation portrait, photographs of Engineering faculty and students, 1926 Class Day and Commencement programs, Gambino's transcripts and a letter of recommendation for him to the Navy, and Gambino's diploma.
  - Classes of 1930-1939, 1926 -- 2008; UA039.001.009
    - Classes, 1930, UA039.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
      Program, Junior Day; Class Day booklet; Program, Senior Banquet; 30th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University, Reunion Photographs, Newsletters from July and August 1975 and November 1971.
    - Classes, 1931, UA039.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
      Program, Class Day; program, Commencement Season; score card, "Tufts vs Harvard", Saturday June 13, 1931; 25th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes (1), 1932, UA039.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
      Program, Class Day; report of the Chairman of the Class Day Committee, 1932.
    - Classes (2), 1932, UA039.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
      40th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1933, UA039.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
      Program, Class Day; program, Chapel Exercises; program, Junior Day; Class Song of 1933; 25th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Mazeppa Don Betts, Jr., class of 1931, personal materials, UA039.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
      Tufts College, class of 1931, class day exercises booklet; Senior banquet, class of 1931 booklet; Commencement 1931, directions for seniors; Tufts College, class of 1931, class day exercises invitation; Tufts College post card, Goddard Chapel, 1926; Personal finances booklet during time at Tufts; Official transcript, 1933; Annual grade report, 1929-1930; Tufts College junior day announcement, May 3, 1930; Tufts College, Twenty-Eighth Annual Visitors' Night, engineering school; Seven Songs of Tufts College, Fourteenth Tufts Night at the Pops, June 16, 1927; Tufts College Bulletin, The Engineering School Number, January, 1931; small envelope of campus photographs. Materials donated by Jane Whitney, September 24, 2007, daughter of Mazeppa Don Betts, Jr.
    - Classes (1), 1934; UA039.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
      Program, Senior Promenade; program, Class Day; program, Senior Banquet; program, Chapel Exercises Class Day; class photo; Class Song of 1934; report of the Class day Commitee
    - Classes (2), 1934; UA039.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet.
    - Classes (3), 1935; UA039.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes (1 of 2), 1935; UA039.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
      Program, Class Day; Class Song of 1935, "Te Salut Amus"; advert, National Tufts Banquet; 50th anniversary booklet; correspondence; Tufts College bulletin.
    - Classes (2 of 2), 1935; UA039.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, Medical School.
    - Classes, 1936; UA039.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson.
    - Classes, 1936; UA039.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
      Program, Class Day; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 30th reunion booklet, Tufts Jackson; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1937; UA039.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet; Tufts-Jackson.
    - Classes, 1937; UA039.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
      Program, Class day; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1937; UA039.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
      35th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1938; UA039.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
      25th reunion, Tufts Jackson; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; beanie.
    - Classes, 1938; UA039.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
      Program, invitation, Class Day; report of the Chairman of the Class day Committee; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson, 45th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1938; UA039.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
    - Classes, 1939; UA039.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
      Program, Class Day; 25th reunion, Tufts Jackson; 25th reunion, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1939; UA039.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
      50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 49th Annual Mid-Winter Meeting and Banquet Program, Tufts College Dental Association; 25th Reunion Class Program (with insert of alumni and addresses), Tufts University School of Dental Medicine.
    - Report of Class Day Committee, 1939; UA039.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
      Report of Class Day Committee submitted by James G. Weldon, Chairman and Albert M. Pearson, Vice-Chairman.
    - 25th Reunion Plaque for the Class of 1935, 1960; UA039.001.017.00001 (Box Shared 138)
      Blue and white tile featuring the Tufts seal and "25th Reunion Class of 1935" bordered in wood; donated by Donna Hersey Sandin.
    - Elephant Bracelet, 1934, UA039.001.018.00009 (Box 18)
      Bracelet features miniature elephants and the Tufts Seal; it is engraved on the back with "Prom 1934;" donated by Donna Hersey Sandin.
    - Alabama grail, UA039.001.018.00013 (Box 18)
      Small silver grail with the inscription "Alabama grail"; donated by Frank Hood (A30), received April 14, 1980. Robert Hood is in the alumni directory as the class of 1930, but his name does not appear in the registry of students in the course catalogs. He does, however, appear in the 1929 Jumbo.
    - Class of 1930 photographs, 1965 -- 1980; UA039.001.056.00014 (Box 56)
    - Class of 1931 photographs, UA039.001.057.00001 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1932 photographs, UA039.001.057.00002 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1933 photographs, UA039.001.057.00003 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1933 photographs (Irving M. Sheppard's D'33 unbound album of Tufts School of Dental Medicine pgs. 1-16), UA039.001.057.00004 (Box 57)
      Unbound photo album of Irving M. Sheppard D'33 donated by Stephen M. Sheppard.
      Dental students; School of Dental Medicine, records
    - Class of 1933 photographs (Irving M. Sheppard's D'33 unbound album of Tufts School of Dental Medicine pgs. 17-32), UA039.001.057.00005 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1934 photographs, UA039.001.057.00006 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1935 photographs, UA039.001.057.00007 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1935 photographs, UA039.001.057.00008 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1936 photographs, UA039.001.057.00009 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1936 photographs, UA039.001.057.00010 (Box 57)
    - Class of 1931 photograph, UA039.001.057.00011 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
    - Class of 1931, Commencement Committee photograph, UA039.001.057.00012 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.058.00001 (Box 58)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.058.00002 (Box 58)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.058.00003 (Box 58)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.058.00004 (Box 58)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.058.00005 (Box 58)
    - 50th Reunion photograph, class of 1937, 1987; UA039.001.058.00007 (Box Shared 35)
      Accompanying material identifies people in the photograph. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Note its different location; it is housed in a separate box with other oversize materials.
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.059.00001 (Box 59)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.059.00002 (Box 59)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.059.00003 (Box 59)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.059.00004 (Box 59)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.059.00005 (Box 59)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.060.00001 (Box 60)
    - Class of 1937 photographs, UA039.001.060.00002 (Box 60)
    - Class of 1938 photographs, UA039.001.060.00003 (Box 60)
    - Class of 1939 photographs, UA039.001.060.00004 (Box 60)
    - Photograph, 1936; UA039.001.065.00001 (Box Shared 66)
    - Class of 1930 pewter pitcher, UA039.001.076.00002 (Box Shared 81)
    - Two Class of 1930 sashes, UA039.001.078.00001 (Box 78)
      purple with gold lettering; probably from a class reunion. No Date Available. Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Button: blue with elephant and number "30", UA039.001.078.00002 (Box 78)
      possibly from class reunion. Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Button: Brown with "Tufts" in blue and '30, UA039.001.078.00003 (Box 78)
      possibly from class reunion. Date Not Available. Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Key Fob, 1930; UA039.001.078.00004 (Box 78)